欢迎朋友们来到 Infobae 的另一版 Random，我和一位很棒的客人在一起
Welcome friends to another edition of Random here at Infobae, I'm with a great guest
Bienvenidos amigos a otra edición de Random aquí en Infobae, estoy con un invitadazo
非常特别的是，他回到了河流，他是世界冠军，所有人都爱他，我什至有很多与海湾有关的问题
very special that he returned to river that he is world champion that all the people love him and I even have many questions related to bay
muy especial que volvió a river que es campeón del mundo que toda la gente lo quiere e incluso tengo muchas preguntas con tema bahía
这让我感兴趣。
that interest me.
que me interesan a mí.
Germán Pescella 先生就在我们身边，欢迎 Germán。
Mr. Germán Pescella is with us, welcome Germán.
El señor Germán Pescella está con nosotros, bienvenido Germán.
一切都很好，谢谢。
All good thanks.
Todo bien, gracias.
很高兴吧？
A pleasure, huh?
Un gustazo, ¿eh?
还是谢谢大家了。
Thanks all the same.
Gracias, igualmente.
非常感谢你们，河流人民，马蒂，媒体，每个人，你们的经理，达里奥，每个来到这里的人。
Thank you very much to you, the people of River, to Mati, the press, to everyone, to your manager, to Darío, to everyone for being here.
Muchas gracias a vos, la gente de River, a Mati, prensa, a todos, a tu manager, a Darío, a todos por estar acá.
经过一年的忙碌和即将结束，我们实现了这一目标。
We have achieved this after a year that has been busy and is ending.
Hemos logrado después de un año que ha sido movidito y que está finalizando.
能和你牵手，非常感激。
to have this hand in hand with you, so super grateful.
tener este mano a mano con vos, así que súper agradecido.
不，谢谢，我很高兴。
No, thanks, my pleasure.
No, gracias, un placer.
今年很忙碌，很高兴。
A pleasure to be busy this year.
Un placer estar un año movido.
感动了，感动了。
Moved, moved.
Movido, movido.
让我们从第一个最美丽的部分开始，因为那是今年，我已经迷路了。
Let's start with the first most beautiful part, because it was this year and I'm already lost.
Empecemos por la primera parte más linda, porque fue este año y yo ya me pierdo.
你回到了河流。
You returned to River.
Volviste a River.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
当它出现时，我不知道是谁，但加拉多，当第一个电话出现时，他们向你抛出这个想法。
When it comes up, I don't know who, but Gallardo, when the first call comes up and they throw the idea at you.
Cuando surge no sé quién, si Gallardo, cuando surge el primer llamado y te tiran la idea.
嘿，德国人，你可以回到河边去。
Hey, Germán, you can go back to the River.
Oye, Germán, podés volver al River.
你的第一感觉是？
Your first sensation?
¿Tu primera sensación?
这整年都充满动力，因为我在贝蒂斯开始了前六个月，显然
It was motivating all year because I started the first six months at Betis and obviously
Fue movilizante todo el año porque yo arranqué los primeros seis meses en el Betis y obviamente
几个月前他们就表示有兴趣让我回来。
They expressed their interest in me returning several months ago.
El interés de que vuelva me lo manifestaron hace varios meses.
我脑子里已经有了一点这个想法，也有想要来这里的感觉。
And I already had the idea in my head a little bit and also the feeling of wanting to be here.
Y yo ya tenía en mi cabeza un poco la idea y también la sensación de querer estar acá.
显然我需要一些时间和家人一起处理这件事。
Obviously I needed some time to process it with my family.
Obviamente necesitaba un tiempo para procesarlo junto con mi familia.
并真正认识到我们的感受。
and really recognize what we were feeling.
y realmente reconocer lo que estábamos sintiendo.
有一天我说，我想回去。
And there was a day when I said, I want to go back.
Y hubo un día que dije, me quiero volver.
我想回去，我需要回去并且好好地回去。
I want to go back, I need to go back and well.
Quiero volver, necesito volver y bueno.
然后渐渐地它开始发生。
Then little by little it began to happen.
Después poco a poco se fue dando.
这很艰难，也很漫长，因为最终我也是俱乐部的一员……
It was hard, it was long, because in the end I was also part of a club that...
Fue duro, fue largo, porque al final yo también era parte de un club que...
他总是对我很好，他们值得我尊重。
He always treated me spectacularly, they deserve all my respect.
Siempre me trató espectacular, se merecen todos mis respetos.
当然，因为你去了贝蒂斯，然后去了佛罗伦萨。
Of course, because you went to Betis, then Fiorentina.
Claro, porque vos fuiste al Betis, después Fiorentina.
然后你回到贝蒂斯，对吗？
And then you returned to Betis, correct?
Y después volviste a Betis, ¿correcto?
显然是在河之前。
Before River, obviously.
Previo a River, obviamente.
来这里之前几个月，我们又续签了几年的合同。
Months before coming here, we signed a contract renewal for several more years.
meses antes de venir para acá, firmamos una renovación de contrato por varios años más.
因为那就是当时发生在我身上的事情。
because that was what was happening to me at that moment.
porque era lo que en ese momento me estaba pasando.
对于我告诉你的，他们如何对待我以及他们给予我的爱。
For what I'm telling you, how they treated me and the love they gave me.
Por esto que te digo, cómo me trataban y el cariño que me daban.
就像有一个计划。
There was like a plan.
Había como un plan.
时时刻刻，这种感觉开始让他需要回来，他考虑着他们。
and from one moment to the next the sensation began to make him need to return, he considered them.
y de un momento para el otro la sensación empezó a hacer la necesidad de volver, se los planteó.
对他们来说，他们知道如何理解我的愿望，事实是他们帮助了我们，让我们能够来到这里。
to them and they knew how to understand what my desire was and the truth is they helped us so that we can be here.
a ellos y supieron entender cuál era mi deseo y la verdad nos ayudaron para que podamos estar acá.
你有没有看到他在嘴里说，如果他叫你里克尔，metatatá，整个笑话？
Did you see that in his mouth he says, if he calls you Riquel, metatatá, that whole joke?
¿Viste que en boca dice, si te llama Riquel, metatatá, todo ese chiste?
Gallardo Directo 给你打电话了吗？领导们给你打电话了吗？
Does Gallardo Directo call you, do the leaders call you?
¿Te llama Gallardo Directo, te llaman los dirigentes?
关系的类型是什么样的？
What is the type of relationship like?
¿Cómo es el tipo de relación?
外面的人不知道。
People out there don't know.
La gente por ahí no sabe.
目前马塞洛接任...
At the moment Marcelo takes over...
En el momento que Marcelo asume...
我实际上正在收拾行李准备回去......
I was practically packing my bags to go back to...
Yo estaba prácticamente con las valijas para volverme a...
去西班牙，因为这没有发生，我们已经聊了几个月了......
to Spain because it didn't happen, we had been chatting for a few months and...
a España porque no se daba, ya veníamos de hace unos meses charlando y...
但这并没有发生，因为我的俱乐部也有条件……
and it didn't happen because my club also had conditions that...
y no se daba porque también mi club tenía unas condiciones que...
它需要被实现，但它没有发生，在某一时刻，它就像……
that it needed to be fulfilled and it wasn't happening and at one point it's like...
que necesitaba que se cumplan y no se daba y en un momento es como que...
我并不是告诉你我们已经认输了，但我差点就坐了三天的航班返回西班牙。
I'm not telling you that we had thrown in the towel, but I almost had a three-day flight to return to Spain.
No te digo que habíamos tirado la toalla, pero ya casi yo tenía un vuelo tres días para volver a España.
啊，我的意思是，你已经说过，酷，准备好了，再见河。
Ah, I mean, you already said, cool, ready, bye River.
Ah, o sea, vos ya decías, guay, listo, chau River.
它不会发生。
It doesn't happen.
No se da.
那将是另一个时间，马塞洛只是假设，马塞洛打电话给我，我已经告诉他了。
It will be at another time and Marcelo just assumes, Marcelo called me and I already told him.
será en otro momento y justo asume Marcelo, me llamó Marcelo y ya le manifesté.
那么直接，德国人是做什么的？
So straight, what does Germán do?
Así directo, ¿qué hace Germán?
关系好吗？
Good relationship?
¿Buena relación?
是的，他想拥有我。
Yes, he would like to have me.
Sí, que a él le gustaría contar conmigo.
我的情况如何，我告诉他情况如何，我的意愿......
and how my situation was and I told him what the situation was like and that my will...
y cómo estaba mi situación y yo le dije cómo era la situación y que mi voluntad...
如果他愿意，那就在这里。
If he wanted, it was to be here.
Si él quería, era estar acá.
两天后他重新启动了一切。
And in two days he reactivated everything.
Y en dos días reactivó todo.
救世主来了。
The Savior arrived.
Llegó el Salvador.
而我却没有上飞机。
And I didn't get on the plane.
Y no me subí al avión.
明显地...
Obviously...
Obviamente...
据贝蒂斯说，我没有上飞机，所以他们可以完成文书工作，然后我就离开了。
According to Betis, I didn't get on the plane so they could finish the paperwork and I left.
De acuerdo con el Betis, no me subí al avión para que puedan terminar los papeles y arranqué.
连你也没想到。
You didn't even expect it either.
Ni te la esperabas tampoco.
事实是否定的。
The truth is no.
La verdad que no.
从那时起，达里奥就在镜头后面。
From there Darío was behind the camera.
De ahí Darío estaba atrás de cámara.
他将会受苦。
He will have suffered.
Habrá sufrido.
工作越多，他的期望就越少。
He expected less after he worked more.
Él se la esperaba menos después que trabajó más.
当然，我工作更多。
I work more, of course.
Trabajo más, claro.
这些过程会让你感到压力吗？
And do those processes stress you out?
Y esos procesos, ¿te estresan?
你33岁了吗？
Are you 33?
¿Vos tenés 33?
压力大吗？
Was it stressful?
¿Te estresan?
您是否已经习惯了足球世界的所有压力以及您可能不喜欢的事情？
Have you already gotten used to all the stress of the football world, of the things that perhaps you don't like?
¿Ya te acostumbraste a todo el estrés del mundo fútbol, de las cosas que quizás no te gustan?
我不会对你撒谎，这让我压力很大。
I'm not going to lie to you, it stressed me out.
No te voy a mentir, me estresó.
这让我压力很大，因为它非常激励我。
It stressed me out because it was very motivating.
Me estresó porque era muy movilizante.
感伤地，对我们的生活、对我的家人、对每个人都非常感动。
sentimentally, very moving for our life, for my family, for everyone.
sentimentalmente, muy movilizante para nuestra vida, para mi familia, para todos.
因此，当事情没有发生并且让你感到沮丧时，然后事情发生了，你就在等待电话或确认。
So when it doesn't happen and it frustrates you and then it's happening and you're waiting for a call or some confirmation.
Entonces cuando no se da y te frustra y después se está dando y estás esperando una llamada o alguna confirmación
虽然压力很大，但最后还是好的……
It's stressful, but good in the end...
es estresante, pero bueno al final...
一切美好的事物也是有代价的。
Everything nice also costs.
Todo lo lindo también cuesta.
与阿根廷一起获得世界冠军的事实，对吗？
The fact of being world champion with Argentina, right?
El hecho de ser campeón del mundo con Argentina ¿no?
我不知道有多少个早晨你醒来后突然说，呃，我是世界冠军，我忘了。
I don't know how many mornings you wake up and suddenly say, uh, I'm a world champion, I had forgotten.
que no sé cuántas mañanas te levantás y de repente decís, uh, soy campeón del mundo, me había olvidado.
这是否与国家队的感觉和恶心的感觉以及你在这种情况下回到国家有关？
Did it have to do with the sensation and that gross feeling that there is with the national team and that you return to the country in this context?
¿Tuvo que ver con la sensación y ese feeling grosso que hay con la selección y que vos vuelvas al país en este contexto?
获得世界冠军后，这与感伤有什么关系吗？
post world champion, did it have anything to do with sentimentality?
post campeón del mundo, ¿tuvo algo que ver en lo sentimental?
不知道和上一篇有没有关系。
I don't know if it had anything to do with the previous one.
No sé si en la previa tuvo algo que ver.
是的，这让我很惊讶，因为我已经融入了阿根廷的日常生活。
Yes, it was something that surprised me a lot since I was already in daily life here in Argentina.
Sí, fue algo que me sorprendió mucho al estar ya en el día a día acá en Argentina.
人们在街上或任何地方的人对待我的方式
of the way people treat me on the street or in any place that someone
de el trato de la gente para conmigo en la calle o en cualquier lugar que alguien
认出我或看到我。
recognizes me or sees me.
me reconoce o que me ve.
现在，无论你是哪支球队的粉丝，这种情况都已成为一种现象，这种情况在我身上发生过很多次。
That now becomes something regardless of the team you are a fan of, that has happened to me a lot.
que ya pasa a ser algo independientemente del equipo del cual es hincha, me ha pasado que mucho.
很多来自 Fanboca 的家伙过来和我合影，并告诉我我是 Fanboca，但是......
Many guys from Fanboca come and take a photo with me and tell me I'm Fanboca but...
muchos chicos de hinchaboca vienen y sacan una foto conmigo y me dicen yo soy hinchaboca pero...
这种选择超越了一切，这让你震惊，它让你震惊，因为在我们生活的社会中......
That selection surpassed everything and that shocks you, it shocks you because in the society we live in...
Esa selección superó todo y a uno eso le impacta, le choca porque en la sociedad que vivimos...
人们最终有能力区分……当然。
That people have that ability in the end to differ between... Of course.
Que la gente tenga esa capacidad al final de diferir entre... Claro.
今天我在River，一位其他俱乐部的球迷与你合影。
Today I'm in River and a fan of other clubs takes a photo with you.
que hoy estoy en River y hincha de otros clubes se saca una foto con vos.
它可以帮助您确定选择过程的范围。
It helps you dimension what the selection process was.
te ayuda a dimensionar lo que fue el proceso en la selección.
但我认为先验的并不是它有那么重。
but I think that a priori it was not that it weighed that much.
pero creo que a priori no fue que pesó tanto.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
我从你母亲那里听到了一个故事，当时他们带着他们的孩子从巴伊亚来到河滨。
I heard a story from your mother when they came from Bahía to River with their
Escuché una historia de tu mamá cuando se vinieron de Bahía a River con sus
伴随着我们所有来自内心的父母所做出的通常的牺牲和痛苦等等。
with the usual sacrifice that any parent has of all of us who are from the interior of coming here and the sufferings and so on.
con el sacrificio habitual que tiene cualquier padre de todos los que somos del interior de venir acá y los sufrimientos y demás.
今天，当你这样回望时，不知道你是不是有一半的怀旧，看着，感慨。
Today, when you look back like this, I don't know if you're half nostalgic, you look and you get emotional.
Hoy, cuando mirás para atrás así, no sé si sos medio nostálgico, mirás y te emocionás.
看看我们走过的路，看看我母亲为之奋斗的道路。
Look at the path we traveled, what my mother fought for.
Mirá el camino que recorrimos, lo que luchó mi vieja.
我很兴奋，但我为变得更好而兴奋，因为最终我认为这是赋予价值的方式......
I get excited, but I get excited for the better because in the end I think it's the way to give value to...
Me emociono, pero me emociono para bien porque al final creo que es la manera de darle valor a...
感谢所有与我们在一起的人的努力，因为最终
to the efforts of all the people who are with us, because in the end
al esfuerzo de toda la gente que está con nosotros, porque al final
也许我们是一切事物的一小部分的可见面孔。
Maybe we are the visible face of a little bit of everything.
Quizá nosotros somos la cara visible un poco de todo.
所有这些努力以及一路上帮助我们的许多人使我们能够
all that effort and so many people who have helped us along the way so that we can
todo ese esfuerzo y tanta gente que nos ha ayudado en el camino para que nosotros podamos
今天轮到我坐在这里谈论什么......
Today it's my turn to be sitting here and talking about what...
Hoy a mí me toca estar sentado acá y hablando de lo que...
我在哪里以及我取得了什么成就。
where I am and what I have achieved.
de dónde estoy y de lo que he conseguido.
怀旧也许就是源于此，它源于赋予所有那些对一个人有帮助的事物的价值和重要性。
and nostalgia perhaps comes from that, it comes from giving value and importance to all those things that help one.
y la nostalgia quizá pasa por eso, pasa por darle valor e importancia a todas esas cosas que lo ayudan a uno.
当他们决定或你决定时，当他们和你母亲一起来时，你多大了？
And when they decided or you decided, when they came with your mother, how old were you?
Y cuando decidieron o decidiste, cuando vinieron con tu mamá, ¿cuántos años tenías?
刚满15岁。
Just turned 15.
15 recién cumplidos.
你有发言权、投票权和意见吗？
Did you have a voice and vote and opinion?
¿Tenías voz y voto y opinión?
妈妈，我们去上学吗？
Mom, are we going to school?
¿Mamá, vamos al colegio?
情况是这样的，我来证明自己是一个来自内陆的男孩，他看到了一个非常遥远的梦想，并说，好吧，我要利用它
The situation was that, I came to prove myself as a boy from the interior who saw a very distant dream and saying well, I'm going to take advantage of it with
la situación fue esa yo vine a probarme como un chico del interior que veía un sueño muy lejano y diciendo bueno voy a aprovechar con
去了解River，然后他们就会踢我，我就会回到巴伊亚。
Get to know River and then they're going to kick me and I'm going to return to Bahía.
Conocer River y después me van a dar una patada y voy a volver a Bahía.
想象
imagine
Imaginate.
我的意思是，你没有那么大的信心。
I mean, you didn't have that much faith.
O sea, no te tenías tanta fe.
我们正在说话。
We are talking.
Estamos hablando.
18年前，这个话题在网络上还没有那么多，一切都很遥远。
18 years ago and the topic was not so much on the networks, it was all very distant.
18 años atrás y no estaba tanto el tema en las redes, era todo muy lejano.
我不知道河里人的水平，我无法和河里的娟子们相比。
I didn't know the level of the River people, I couldn't compare my level with the Juan boys in River.
Yo no sabía el nivel de la gente de River, no podía comparar mi nivel con los chicos Juan en River.
当我来测试自己时，事实是，我感觉很好。
And when I came to test myself, the truth is, I felt good.
Y cuando vine a probarme, la verdad, me sentí bien.
接下来的一周，他回到了另一个预科，他们告诉我我必须留下来。
The following week he returned to another pre and they told me I had to stay.
A la semana siguiente volvió a otra pre y me dijeron que me tenía que quedar.
在那里，我的老人看着我，告诉我他想做什么。
And there my old man looked at me and told me what he wanted to do.
Y ahí mi viejo me miró y me dijo qué quería hacer.
我想都没想就告诉他我想留下来。
And I told him, without even thinking about it, that I want to stay.
Y yo le dije, sin pensarlo de vez, que yo me quiero quedar.
当我知道这一点后，就没有回头路了。
After I learned this, there is no turning back.
Después que conocí esto, no hay vuelta atrás.
您在巴伊亚上高中吗？
Were you in high school in Bahia?
¿Vos estabas en la secundaria en Bahía?
是的，是的，我当时是高中生。
Yes, yes, I was in high school.
Sí, sí, estaba en la secundaria.
所以你也必须重新考虑，在 River 而不是在学校完成学业。
So you also had to rethink, finishing your studies at River rather than at school.
O sea que tenías que también replantear, terminar en River los estudios que en la escuela.
我猜是River的学校。
River's school I guess.
La escuela de River supongo.
是的，最终在 River，我们从小时候起就一直享有特权，因为我们的支持
Yes, in the end at River we were always privileged since I was a child because the support
Sí, al final en River siempre fuimos privilegiados desde chico porque el sostén
他们给我们的这个对于我的家人来说非常大，也非常重要。
and the one they gave us was very big for my family, it was very important too.
y el que nos han dado era muy grande para mi familia, era muy importante también.
我在俱乐部内有一个住的地方，我有安全保障，我有......
I had a place to live inside the club, I had security, I had...
Yo tenía un lugar donde vivir dentro del club, tenía una seguridad, tenía...
必要的教育，这些都是......
the necessary education and those are things that...
la educación necesaria y eso son cosas que...
他们也让我的父母安心，因为我 15 岁时没有离开巴伊亚
They also left my parents in peace that being 15 years old without having left Bahia
a mis viejos también lo dejaron tranquilo de que teniendo 15 años sin haber salido de Bahía
不仅仅是去附近的城镇。
more than to go to a nearby town.
más que para ir a un pueblo cercano.
把我留在布宜诺斯艾利斯将是一个很好的原型。
Leaving me in Buenos Aires was going to be a good prototype.
Dejarme en Buenos Aires iba a estar bien prototipo.
可以这么说，编织。
woven, so to speak.
tejido, por decirlo de alguna manera.
多么恶心啊。
How gross.
Qué grosso.
Beyense，你距离打篮球有多远，或者你打篮球多久了，或者篮球是什么样的？
Beyense, how far away were you from playing basketball, or how long did you play basketball, or what is basketball like?
Beyense, ¿a cuánto estuviste de jugar al básquet, o cuánto jugaste al básquet, o cómo es tema básquet?
因为没有瓦伦斯不谈论篮球。
Because there is no Vallense who doesn't talk about basketball.
Porque no hay vallense que no hable de básquet.
这是一件事……我小时候很不情愿。
And it's a thing... I was reluctant when I was a kid.
Y es un tema... Era reacio cuando era chico.
因为我是学校里唯一一个以联盟方式踢足球的人，每次我们上体育课时，我们都必须打篮球。
because I was the only one in school who played soccer in a federated way and every time we had physical education we had to play basketball.
porque era el único en el colegio que jugaba el fútbol de manera federada y cada vez que teníamos educación física había que jugar al básquet.
除此之外，他还添加了跳跃。
And on top of that he added jump.
Y encima puso salto.
当然，我喜欢它，但我很不情愿，因为，你看，它与其他人背道而驰。
Of course, and I liked it, but I was reluctant, because it was, you see, going against everyone else.
Claro, y me gustaba, pero era reacio, porque era, viste, llevarle la contra a todo el resto.
我想踢足球，我不想打球。
I want to play soccer, I don't want to play ball.
Yo quiero jugar al fútbol, no quiero jugar al balón.
你应该成为布兰卡港的叛乱者。
You should be a rebel in Bahía Blanca.
Deberías ser un rebelde en Bahía Blanca.
我的队友总是打篮球。
My teammates always played basketball.
Mis compañeros siempre jugaban al básquet.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
随着时间的推移，他确实喜欢上了它，我并不是说我玩它。
and then over time he did get a taste for it, I'm not saying that I play it.
y después con el tiempo sí le fue agarrando el gusto, no digo que lo juego.
我为自己辩护，但我喜欢它，我很感兴趣。
I defend myself, but I like it, I'm very interested.
Me defiendo, pero me gusta, me interesa mucho.
国家队里有很多他们喜欢、踢球的球员。
There is a lot in the national team that they like and play.
Hay mucho en la selección que les guste y juegan.
嗯，他们看 NBA 是为了看比赛。
Well, they watch NBA for the games.
Bueno, miran NBA por los partidos.
是的，嗯，我有这种兴趣。
Yes, well, I have that intrigue.
Sí, bueno, tengo esa intriga.
他之所以能成为那样的球员，是因为迪布，如果有一天我看到他罚球的话，我就知道了。
He was in that one because of Dibu, I know if I saw him shooting some free throws one day.
Estaba en esa por el Dibu, lo sé si lo vi tirando unos tiros libres un día.
这幅画是一场灾难。
The drawing is a disaster.
El Dibu es un desastre.
这幅画是一场灾难。
The drawing is a disaster.
El Dibu es un desastre.
我们杀了他。
We kill him.
Lo matamos.
埃尔迪布来自马德普拉塔，也是一名篮球运动员。
El Dibu comes from Mar del Plata, also a basketball player.
El Dibu viene de Mar del Plata, también basquetbolera.
但不，抽签是一场灾难。
But no, the Draw is a disaster.
Pero no, el Dibu es un desate.
谁射得好？
Who shoots well?
¿Quién tira bien?
劳塔罗投篮很好，他的兄弟打篮球，杰罗鲁利投篮也很好。
Lautaro shoots well, his brother plays basketball, Gero Rulli shoots well.
Lautaro tira bien, el hermano juega el básquet, Gero Rulli tira bien.
有一个长矛，偶尔我们会发现一个箍。
There is a pike, occasionally we find a hoop.
Hay una pica, de vez en cuando encontramos un aro.
一个贵族，他们在那里流行起来。
An aristo and they catch on there.
Un aristo y se prenden ahí.
多厚，多厚。
How thick, how thick.
Que grosso, que grosso.
听着，例如，来自巴伊亚的您有没有联系过？
Listen, and from Bahia for example, did you ever have any contact?
Escucha, y de Bahía por ejemplo, ¿tuviste algún contacto alguna vez?
马努·吉诺比利是河床球迷，不是这样的球迷，但他就是河床球迷。
Manu Ginobili is a River fan, not such a fan, but he is a River fan.
Manu Ginobili es un fan de River, no tan fanático, pero es de River.
您与他们中的任何人进行过交谈吗？
Did you have talks with any of them?
¿Tuviste charlas con alguno de ellos?
你能遇到吗？
Were you able to come across?
¿Pudiste cruzarte?
看，作为一个孩子，我从来没有机会，他们总是在我身边......
Look, as a kid I never had the chance, they were always there for me...
Mirá, de chico no había tenido nunca la posibilidad, siempre ellos fueron para mí...
除了运动之外，它们还是参考。
Beyond sport, they were references.
más allá del deporte, fueron referentes.
因为最终这就是我们总是谈论的，从内部出发，做马努、佩佩·桑切斯所做的事情。
because in the end that is what we always talk about, coming from within and doing what Manu did, what Pepe Sánchez did.
porque al final es lo que hablamos siempre, venir del interior y hacer lo que hizo Manu, lo que hizo Pepe Sánchez.
蒙泰基亚，很多人都曾为国家队效力过。
Montecchia, many people who have played for the national team.
Montecchia, mucha gente que ha jugado en la selección.
做他们所做的事情是非常困难的。
Doing what they did is very difficult.
hacer lo que hicieron ellos es muy difícil.
然后显然你会看到马努和马努......
Then obviously you see Manu and Manu...
Después obviamente ves a Manu y Manu...
历史上最伟大的阿根廷运动员。
of the greatest Argentine athletes in history.
de los deportistas argentinos más grandes de la historia.
你试图认同这项运动中的那些方式和价值观。
You try to identify with those ways, with those values ​​within the sport.
Intentás identificarte con esas maneras, con esos valores dentro del deporte.
然后我就没有机会了，几个月前
then I had not had the opportunity and a few months ago
entonces no había tenido la oportunidad y hace unos meses
在巴伊亚发生风暴灾难之后。
after the catastrophe that happened in Bahia through the storm.
después de la catástrofe que pasó en Bahía a través del temporal.
我有机会与他们交谈了很多，因为我们为了追求这一事业而聚集在一起。
I had the chance to talk a lot with them because we came together a little in pursuit of that cause.
Tuve la posibilidad de hablar mucho con ellos porque nos unimos un poco en pos de esa causa.
没什么，他们是完全正常的孩子，但是嘿，最后人们认为这是......
And nothing, they are totally normal kids, but hey, in the end one sees it as...
Y nada, son pibes totalmente normales, pero bueno, al final uno lo ve como...
对我来说，他们是如此正常，因此他们来自另一个星球。
For me they are so normal that they are from another planet for that reason.
Para mí son tan normales que son de otro planeta por eso.
因为成就并不等于……最终，当你遇到那些达到如此高度的人时……
Because achievement is not coincident with... In the end, when you meet those types of people who have reached so high...
Porque el logro no es coincidente con... Al final, cuando conoces ese tipo de personas que han llegado tan alto...
您意识到每个人都有这种类型的共同点。
You realize that everyone has a common denominator of that type.
te das cuenta que todos tienen un común denominador de ese tipo.
听我说，你曾经一度担任队长，我不知道这是否是巧合，那是一场多么好的比赛，在卡塔尔预选赛之前，对吧？
Listen to me, you had to be captain at one point, I don't know if it was coincidence, it was what a match, prior to the Qatar qualifier, right?
Escúchame, te tocó ser capitán en un momento, no sé si fue casual, fue un partido qué, previo eliminatoria de Qatar, ¿no es cierto?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
例如，当阿根廷队队长更难还是当父亲更难？
Is it more difficult to be captain of the Argentine team or is it more difficult to be a father, for example?
¿Es más difícil ser capitán de la selección argentina o es más difícil ser papá, por ejemplo?
我仍然不能和你谈论成为一名父亲，但我想成为一名父亲是一个很大的痛苦。
I still can't talk to you about being a dad, but I imagine it's a big pain to be a dad.
Todavía no puedo hablarte de ser papá, pero imagino que es un cagazo grande ser papá.
我和有孩子的同事分享，但是......
and I share it with my colleagues who have children, but...
y lo comparto con mis compañeros que tienen hijos, pero...
当它触动我的时候，这是一种巨大的自豪……
It is a tremendous pride the times it has touched me...
Es un orgullo tremendo las veces que me ha tocado...
当你看到自己戴着手镯的照片时，我的那一刻就像不太相信，显然是由于没有队友和当时的情况。
My moment is like not quite believing it when you see a photo of yourself with a bracelet, obviously due to the absence of teammates and the circumstance.
Mi momento es como no terminar de creértelo de ver una foto tuya con un brazalete obviamente por la ausencia de compañeros y la circunstancia.
那是看到的。
that is seen.
que se ve.
但它具有巨大的价值。
But it has enormous value.
Pero tiene un valor enorme.
还有20个要给他们，他们给了你。
There are 20 more to give it to them and they gave it to you.
Hay 20 más para dárselo y te lo dieron a vos.
它具有巨大的价值，...
It has enormous value that...
Tiene un valor enorme que...
当，在那一刻，当一个人处于劳动和节奏中时，
that when, at that moment, one when one is in labor and in the rhythm,
que cuando, en ese momento, uno cuando está en laboraje y en el ritmo,
也许你没有看到全貌，但你会看到一张你自己戴着阿根廷队队长袖标的照片。
Maybe you don't get the full picture, but then you see a photo of yourself wearing the captain's armband of the Argentine team.
Quizás no tomás total dimensión, pero después ves una foto tuya con el brazalete de capitán de la selección argentina.
的受害者。
of the victims.
de las víctimas.
妈的，这有点引出了上一件事，说那个人所走的路
Shit this leads a bit to the previous thing to say the path one takes for that guy
Mierda esto lleva un poco a lo anterior a decir el camino que uno recorre para ese tipo
的情况。
of situations.
de situaciones.
第一个召唤你的是圣保利，斯卡洛尼所在的地方。
The first one that summons you is San Paoli, where Scaloni was.
El primero que te convoca es San Paoli, donde estaba Scaloni.
正确，然后我会再次召唤你斯卡罗尼，从那时起
correct and then I will summon you again Scaloni, at that beginning
correcto y después te vuelvo a convocar Scaloni, en ese inicio
你以为每个人都这么做，但他最终会成为今天的伟大教练吗？
You thought everyone did, but that he was going to end up being the great coach he is today?
pensabas que todos, pero que él iba a terminar siendo el técnico tan grosso que es hoy?
我认为没有人...我的意思是，Escalón 所经历的演变以及超越它当然是由标题支持的，对吗？
I don't think anyone... I mean, the evolution that Escalón had and beyond that is supported, of course, by the titles, right?
Creo que nadie lo... O sea, la evolución que tuvo Escalón y más allá que lo avalan, por supuesto, los títulos, ¿no?
但当你看到他踢球时，我认为人们会认同他，我喜欢这个阿根廷，我喜欢这个人。
But when you see him play, I think people identify with him. I like this Argentina and I like this guy.
pero cuando vos lo ves jugar yo creo que la gente se identifica uuuh esta Argentina me gusta y este chabón me gusta.
我认为没有人，即使是最乐观的人......
I think that no one, not even the most optimistic...
Creo que nadie, ni el más optimista...
我认为循环可以这样发展。
I thought the cycle could go that way.
pensaba que el ciclo podía ir de esa manera.
同样，在第一场比赛中，他总是不断地重复说他是临时的六场比赛或六场著名的比赛。
The same in the first games he always constantly repeated that he was temporary for six games or six famous ones.
El mismo los primeros partidos siempre repetía constantemente de que él estaba temporal por seis partidos o seis famosos
这场比赛一直持续到年底。
game that was until the end of the year.
partido que había hasta fin de año.
随着比赛的进行，比赛的进行，他也找到了一种方法
and as it went on, the competition, the games, he also found a way
y a medida que fue pasando, la competencia, los partidos, él fue también encontrando la manera
这最适合团队。
that suited the team best.
que mejor le sentaba al equipo.
2019 年美洲杯是一个转折点。
The 2019 Copa América was a turning point.
La Copa América del 2019 fue un punto de quiebre.
在杯赛的中间，他也许以一种很好的方式诠释
in the middle of the Cup, he perhaps interprets in a good way
en medio de la Copa, él quizá interpreta de buena manera
球队需要的比赛方式，当时版本中的名字需要的方式。
The way of playing that the team needed, that the names that were in that edition at that time needed.
La manera de jugar que el equipo necesitaba, que los nombres que en ese momento estaban en esa edición necesitaba.
那一刻我们感到，切...
And we felt at that moment, che...
Y nosotros sentimos en ese momento, che...
这真的可以走路。
This can walk, seriously.
Esto puede caminar, en serio.
除此之外，我们在半决赛中输给了巴西。
Beyond the fact that we lost the semifinal with Brazil.
Más allá de que perdimos la semifinal con Brasil.
我们获得了第三名，但我们看到了一些东西
We won third place but we saw that there was something
ganamos el tercer puesto pero veíamos que había algo
正在创建的东西可能很重要。
something that was being created that could be important.
algo que se estaba creando que podía ser importante.
发生这一切之后...
After everything that happens...
Después todo lo que pasa...
这不像你想的那样，哇，我们要成为世界冠军。
It's not like you were thinking, wow, we're going to become world champions.
tampoco es que uno estaba pensando, uy, vamos a salir campeones del mundo.
不，我们认为在下一届美洲杯中我们可能有机会。
No, we are thinking that in the next Copa América we could have a chance.
No, estamos pensando en que la siguiente Copa América podíamos llegar a tener una chance.
事情就是这样，然后是其余的一切。
And so it was, and then all the rest.
Y así fue, y después todo el resto.
剩下的就是历史了。
The rest is history.
El resto es historia.
进化的方式是疯狂的，而且你还得到了 Gallardo 和 Scaloni。
It's crazy how evolution grows, plus you get both Gallardo and Scaloni.
es loco cómo crece la evolución además te tocan tanto Gallardo como Scaloni.
我不知道他们是否是你职业生涯中最好的两位教练，但你至少能告诉我你喜欢他们的哪一点吗？
I don't know if they are the two best coaches of your career, but can you at least tell me what you like about each of them?
No sé si son los dos mejores entrenadores de tu carrera, pero ¿me podés destacar por lo menos qué te gusta a vos de cada uno de ellos?
事实上，Escaloni 的工作非常简单、非常具体。
Escaloni the truth is that it is very simple, very specific in what he
Escaloni la verdad que es muy sencillo, muy concreto en lo que él
团队的要求，也是基于此
asks of the team, also based on that
pide del equipo, también basado en esa
团队已经如此认可的那些方式，今天这个想法还没有被触及。
In those ways that the team has so recognized, today that idea is not touched.
en esas maneras que tiene el equipo tan reconocida, hoy por hoy esa idea no se toca.
但他总会找到两三个
but then he always finds two or three
pero después siempre él encuentra dos o tres
每场比赛都有不同的选择，哪些可以伤害对手，哪些可以保护自己。
alternatives in each match, from which to hurt the rival, from which to defend yourself.
alternativas en cada partido, de la cual hacerle daño al rival, de la cual defenderte.
而马塞洛是一个每天24小时都在与足球呼吸的人，如果他26岁，他就25岁了。
And Marcelo is a person who breathes football 24 hours a day, and if he were 26 he would be 25.
Y Marcelo es una persona que respira a fútbol las 24 horas del día, y si tuviese 26 serían 25.
它向你传递那种信念、那种强度、那种足球生活方式。
and it transmits to you that conviction and that intensity, that way of living football.
y te transmite ese convencimiento y esa intensidad, esa manera de vivir el fútbol.
在每一次谈话中，在每一次培训中，在所做的任何工作中，没有一个可以放松的地方。
In every talk, in every training, in any work one does, there is no place to relax.
En cada charla, en cada entrenamiento, en cualquier trabajo que uno hace, no hay lugar para relajarse.
从那里他提出了他的足球。
And from there he proposes his football.
Y a partir de ahí él propone su fútbol.
激烈的足球，有很多节奏，有很多进攻。
Intensity football, with a lot of rhythm, with a lot of attack.
Fútbol de intensidad, de mucho ritmo, de mucho ataque.
总有一些时刻可以表达得更好或更糟，但这就是想法。
There are always moments in which it can be expressed better or worse, but that is the idea.
Siempre hay momentos en los cuales se puede plasmar mejor o peor, pero su idea es esa.
我希望这个能被记录十年，因为……
I want this to be recorded for 10 years because...
Quiero que esto quede grabado para dentro de 10 años porque...
Niko Tagliafico 在谈论教练技巧和主题时告诉我，Germán Pesce 知道这一点，我过去常常早上 7 点起床。
Niko Tagliafico, talking about coaching techniques and the subject matter, told me, Germán Pesce knows it, I used to get up at 7 in the morning.
Niko Tagliafico hablando de técnicos de coach y cierros de tema me dijo, Germán Pesce la sabe, yo me levantaba a las 7 de la
明天，因为我有欧洲赛程，当我集中注意力时，我必须学习去高中，这样以后我就可以成为一名教练，但现在我不
tomorrow because I had European schedules and when I came to concentrate I had to study to go to high school so that later I could be a coach and now I don't
mañana porque tenía los horarios europeos y cuando venía a concentrarme tocaba para estudiar para dar el secundario para después poder ser entrenador y ahora no
他还没有参加教练课程，但他会达到尼科的水平，就像足球一样。
He hasn't taken the coaching course yet, but he will reach that level Nico, like football.
no hizo el curso de entrenador todavía, pero llegará a ese nivel Nico, como del fútbol.
尼科知道，看看……
And Nico knows, look what...
Y Nico sabe, mira que...
有一天他抓住我并告诉我，事实是有时我们和你一起睡觉......
The other day he grabbed me and told me, the truth is that sometimes we sleep with you that...
El otro día me agarró y me dijo, la verdad que dormimos a veces con vos que...
和我妻子的那件事，正如罗纳尔多当时所说的，你明白吗？
That with my wife, as Ronaldo said that time, you see?
Que con mi mujer, como dijo Ronaldo aquella vez, ¿viste?
因为，与 U-20 一起，直到今天，我们聚集在一起，我们已经彼此了解。
Because, together with the U-20, to this day, we gather together and we already know each other.
Porque, junto de las U-20, hasta el día de hoy, concentrando juntos y ya nos conocemos.
他和你在一起的夜晚肯定比和卡罗在一起的夜晚还要多，这是真的，我得数一数。
He must have had more nights with you than with Karo, it's true, I'll have to count them.
Debe tener más noche con vos que con Karo, es verdad, habré que contarlas.
我们彼此熟识，我们已经知道彼此的日程安排。
We know each other by heart, we already know each other's schedules.
Nos conocemos de memoria, ya sabemos los horarios cada uno.
口味相似，除了动漫和他喜欢的东西我不喜欢。
similar tastes, except anime and those things he likes that I don't like.
gustos similares, menos el anime y esas cosas le gustan a él que a mí no me gustan.
啊，好，好信息。
Ah, well, good information.
Ah, bien, buen dato.
但他开始了教练课程，我也开始了，所以......
But he started the coaching course, I started it too, so...
Pero él arrancó el curso de entrenador, yo lo arranqué también, entonces...
我们分享东西，我们谈论足球，我们谈论NBA，因为他也喜欢NBA。
We share things, we talk about football, we talk about the NBA, because he also likes the NBA.
Compartimos cosas, charlamos de fútbol, charlamos de NBA, porque a él también le gusta la NBA.
事实上，他是一个非常有能力并且对足球也了解很多的男孩。
The truth is that he is a boy who is very capable and who also knows a lot about football.
La verdad es un chico que es muy capaz y que sabe mucho también de fútbol.
怎样才能成为一名好教练呢？
And what can be a good coach?
¿Y que puede ser buen entrenador?
我想是的。
I think so.
Yo creo que sí.
你呢？
And you?
¿Y vos?
让我们来看看。
Let's see.
Vamos a ver.
事实上，这是吸引我的东西。
The truth is that it is something that attracts me.
La verdad que es algo que me atrae.
有点……我们把它扔到了桌子上。
It's a bit... We threw it on the table.
Es un poco... La hemos tirado arriba de la mesa.
啊，显示？
Ah, ¿show?
Ah, ¿viste?
奥乔。
Ojo.
事实是我真的很喜欢足球，看足球。
The truth is I really like football, watching football.
La verdad me gusta mucho el fútbol, mirar el fútbol.
完成学位后，您会看到自己想从事足球的哪个领域。
After finishing your degree you see what sector of football you want to be in.
termine la carrera uno ve en qué sector del fútbol quiere estar.
链接，但这是我喜欢的东西。
linked, but it's something I like.
ligado, pero es algo que me gusta.
听我说，我们谈论巴斯克斯，我们谈论足球、国家队、河床，一切。
Listen to me, we talk about Vázquez, we talk about football, the national team, River, everything.
Escúchame, hablamos de Vázquez, hablamos de fútbol, selección, River, todo.
我知道了，2010年陪练选拔赛，你是马拉多纳的乒乓搭档吗？
I understand, 2010 Sparring Selection, were you Maradona's ping pong partner?
Tengo entendido, 2010 Sparring Selección, eras compañero de ping pong de Maradona?
不，不是我的朋友，但我不得不和迭戈吵架。
No, not my friend, but I had to fight a little with Diego.
No, compañero no, pero me tocó pelotear un poquito con el Diego.
告诉我我打得很好。
Tell me I played well.
Decime que jugaba bien.
是的，他对每个人来说都打得很好。
Yes, he played well to everyone.
Sí, jugaba bien a todos.
这是一件不可思议的事情。
It's an incredible thing.
Es una cosa increíble.
但那些人对每个人来说都表现得很好。
But those people played well to everyone.
Pero esa gente jugaba bien a todos.
但他乒乓球也打得很好。
But he played ping pong well too.
Pero jugaba bien al ping pong también.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
而且我也不想打败他。
And I didn't want to beat him either.
Y tampoco quería ganarle.
如果你能打败他的话...
If you could beat him...
Si le podías ganar…
这个敢打我的小子是谁？
Who is this daring kid who beat me?
¿Quién es este pibe atrevido que me ganó?
但迭戈也把你打倒了。
But Diego took you down too.
Pero Diego te bajaba también.
问题是他把自己降低到了我们的水平、我们的脚步。
The thing is that he lowered himself to our level, to our step.
Es que él se bajaba al nivel, al escalón nuestro.
这样你就不会受苦了。
So that you wouldn't suffer.
Para que vos no sufrieras.
我们正在陪练，一切对我们来说都是新的……
We were sparring and everything was new to us and...
Nosotros estábamos de sparring y estábamos para nosotros todo nuevo y...
出于无聊，我们打乒乓球，小游戏，他过来开始和我们一起玩，当然，我们说……
Out of boredom, we played ping-pong, little games, and he came and started playing with us, and of course, we said...
del aburrimiento, jugábamos al ping-pong, a los jueguitos, y él venía y se ponía a jugar con nosotros, y claro, nosotros decíamos...
这个疯狂的家伙正在和我们打乒乓球，他不知道对于我们来说我们即将死在这里。
This crazy guy is playing ping pong against us and he doesn't know that for us we are just about to die here.
Este loco está jugando ping pong contra nosotros y no sabe que para nosotros es que nos estamos por morir acá nomás.
这是上帝，这是马拉多纳。
It's God, it's Maradona.
Es Dios, es Maradona.
是的，当然，我打完乒乓球，一张一张地拍了照片，第二天又拍了照片。
Yes, of course, I finished playing ping-pong and took photos one by one and the next day took photos again.
Sí, claro, terminaba de jugar al ping-pong y foto uno por uno y al día siguiente foto otra vez.
事实是，这是一场奇观。
The truth is that it was a spectacle.
La verdad que fue un espectáculo.
所以你们进行了一场一对一的战斗。
So you had a little one-on-one fight.
O sea que tuviste un peloteito mano a mano.
一头小而短的头发。
A small, short hair.
Un peledito chiquito, cortito.
不，停下来。
No, stop.
No, dejá.
嘭嘭嘭，嘭嘭嘭。
Pum, pum, pum y chau.
另一件事。
Another thing.
Otra cosa.
然后他似乎认出了你们所有人，因为你们还很小。
And then he seemed to recognize all of you because you were very little.
Y después él como que los iba reconociendo a todos porque ustedes eran muy chiquitos.
是的，那时我们18岁，19岁。
Yes, we were 18, we were 19 at that time.
Sí, teníamos 18, teníamos en ese momento 19.
后来你有机会和迭戈一起看看我到达的地方。
Afterwards you had a chance with Diego to see where I arrived.
Después tuviste chance con Diego de mirar dónde llegué.
不，之后我就不能同意了，因为之后他就离开了国家队。
No, after that I couldn't agree because after that he left the national team.
No, después de eso no pude coincidir porque él después de eso se va de la selección.
他没有在一个能让他想起的地方再次见面。
He did not meet again in a place where it could have made him remember.
no volvía a coincidir en un lugar donde pueda haberle hecho recordar.
当我当教练的时候，我也在陪练，但那是我们的记忆。
I was sparring when I was a coach, but they are memories that remain with us.
Yo estaba de sparring cuando era técnico, pero son recuerdos que nos quedan grabados.
听我说，我不可避免地要问大家，看，从迭戈这让我想起了另一位球星梅西，对吧？
Listen to me, it is inevitable that I ask everyone, look, from Diego it takes me back to the other star, Messi, right?
Escúchame, es inevitable que les pregunte a todos, mira, de Diego me vuelve a llevar al otro crack, a Messi, ¿no?
你拥有更多，你分享更多等等。
that you have it more, that you share more and so on.
que lo tenés más, que compartís más y demás.
我认为梅西是一个我们现在把一切都放在一起的人，完全......
I see Messi as a person who we put everything together now, totally...
Yo lo veo a Messi como una persona que nos ponemos todo armate ahora, totalmente...
就像一个普通的、正常的、基本的、简单的，那不会反映你，对吧？
like an ordinary, normal, base, simple, that is not going to reflect you, right?
como un ordinario, normal, base, simple, que no te va a reflejar, ¿no?
我还听说他是一位非常好的顾问等等。
And I also heard that he is a very good advisor and so on.
Y también escuché que está como muy buen consejero y demás.
你离开他们正在喝酒的房间，伙计，他是世界上最知名的人。
You leave the room where they are drinking mate and he is the most well-known guy in the world.
salís de la habitación donde están tomando mate y es el tipo más conocido del mundo.
梅西在一对一的情况下表现如何？
How is Messi in one-on-one situations there?
¿Cómo es Messi en el mano a mano ahí?
这是我们之前讨论的一部分。
And it's part of what we were talking about before.
Y es parte de lo que hablábamos antes.
他们是那些有共同点的人物和人，这就是你所说的。
They are those types of figures and people who have a common denominator, which is what you say.
Son ese tipo de figuras y de personas que tienen un común denominador que es ese que decís vos.
他们都是完全正常的人，并且习惯了这么多......
They are totally normal people and are used to so much...
Son personas totalmente normales y están acostumbradas a tanta...
暴露并且无法离开家......
exposure and not being able to leave the house that...
exposición y no poder salir de la casa que...
有时你会错误地将他归类为队友，当他们是新人而你来到国家队时，明白吗？
Sometimes you make the mistake of pigeonholing him as a teammate, when they are new and you come to the national team, see?
A veces uno comete el error de encasillarlo en eso como compañero, cuando son nuevos y llegas a la selección, ¿viste?
然后发生了这种情况，你坐下来喝马黛茶，他是宇宙中最正常的人。
And then that happens, you sit down to drink mate and he is the most normal person in the universe.
Y después pasa eso, te sentás a tomar mate y es la persona más normal del universo.
而他也是宇宙中最伟大的足球运动员和最正常的人。
And he is also the greatest footballer and the most normal person in the universe.
Y además es el más grande futbolista y la persona más normal del universo.
还有我，感谢上帝，很多年前了。
And me, thank God, many years ago.
Y yo, gracias a Dios, hace muchos años.
我必须与他分享，今天我对任何事情都进行了完全正常的对话。
I had to share with him and today I have totally normal conversations about anything.
Me ha tocado compartir con él y hoy tengo charlas totalmente normales de cualquier cosa.
生命本身...
of life itself...
de la vida misma...
他在迈阿密的生活怎么样，他过得怎么样？前几天他问我，阿根廷这里怎么样，他过得怎么样？
How does he live there in Miami, how is he having it, how is it? He asked me the other day, what is it like here in Argentina, how is he having it,
cómo vive él allá en Miami, cómo la pasa, qué tal me preguntaba la otra día qué tal acá en Argentina, cómo la estaba pasando,
完全正常的事情，今天对我们来说可能变成了
totally normal things, which today for us perhaps become a
cosas totalmente normales, que hoy para nosotros pasa a ser quizá una
这是一种常态，人们不会进入他的头脑。
a normality and that people don't get into his head.
una normalidad y que la gente no le entre en la cabeza.
别让你以为他是那么正常。
Don't let it get into your head that he is so normal.
Que no le entre en la cabeza que él sea tan normal.
精确的。
Exact.
Exacto.
是如此非凡。
Being so extraordinary.
Siendo tan extraordinario.
精确的。
Exact.
Exacto.
最后，它永远不会停止让我们感到惊讶，因为......
And in the end it never ceases to surprise us just as much because...
Y al final no deja de sorprendernos igual a nosotros porque...
他的一切，他创造的一切，还有那么多双眼睛注视着他，那么多目光，那么多……
with everything he is, with everything he generates and so many eyes on him, so many looks, so much...
con todo lo que es, con todo lo que genera y tantos ojos sobre él, tantas miradas, tanta...
人们演奏他们所做的和不做的事情是非常困难的。
people playing what they do and what they don't do is very difficult.
gente jugando qué hace y qué deja de hacer es muy difícil.
表现得像那样的行为。
behave like that behavior.
comportarse como ese comportamiento.
听我说，我已经知道你感动了，冷静点。
Listen to me, I already know that you moved, calm down.
Escúchame, yo ya sé que te moviste, tranquilo.
梅西走过来说，听我说，我们正在整合一切，你看到了我们在国际米兰所做的一切。
Messi comes and says, listen to me, we are putting things together, you saw what we are putting together at Inter.
Viene Messi y dice, escuchame, estamos armando, viste lo que estamos armando en Inter.
来到迈阿密，达里奥再次工作，毁掉合同，我想，我不知道，我不知道是否......
Come to Miami, Darío to work again, to break contracts, I imagine, I don't know, I don't know if...
Venite para Miami, de nuevo Darío a trabajar, a romper contratos, me imagino, no sé, no sé si...
不，我在电视上看。
No, I watch it on TV.
No, yo lo veo por la tele.
我们在电视上观看并在电视上享受它。
We watch it on TV and we enjoy it on TV.
Lo miramos por la tele y lo disfrutamos por la tele.
因为最重要的是，似乎不是，那就是……
Because on top of that it seems not, that is...
Porque encima parece que no, o sea...
对我来说他还有五年的时间，但我不知道他想要多长时间。
For me he has five more years, but I don't know how much he'll want to.
Para mí tiene para cinco años más, pero no sé cuántas ganas le va a dar.
他想踢多久就踢多久。
And he will play as long as he wants.
Y él va a jugar hasta cuando quiere.
它完好无损。
It is intact.
Está intacto.
有...
Has...
Tiene...
在他的头脑里，他远远领先于其他人
in his head he is far ahead of anyone else
en su cabeza está muy por delante de cualquier otra
足球中间地带的负责人并看到了事情。
head of the middle ground of football and sees things.
cabeza de término medio del fútbol y ve las cosas.
比其他人领先很长时间，这使他能够继续保持快速，这是这里最重要的事情。
a long time before the others and that allows him to continue being fast, which is the most important thing here.
mucho tiempo antes que los demás y eso le permite seguir estando rápido, que es de acá lo más importante.
最后一个话题梅西，你看到他在有球训练中做了一些绝对非凡的事情，每个人都说
last topic Messi, you saw him do something absolutely extraordinary in training with the ball, something that everyone says that
último tema Messi, le viste hacer algo absolutamente extraordinario en un entrenamiento con la pelota algo que todos cuentan que
我不知道这是否有什么特别的，但这是我第一次进入国家队时的经历。
I don't know if it was something in particular, but it stuck in my mind one of the first times in the national team.
No sé si algo en particular, pero me quedó grabado una de las primeras veces en la selección.
我们的队伍减少了三人，而我是他的队伍中的一员。
We were playing with a reduced team of three and I was on his team.
que estábamos jugando a un reducido en tres equipos y a mí me tocó en su equipo.
我们必须从外面开始，我们进去，他们消灭了另一支球队，他们在禁区外投了一颗炸弹，进球了。
We had to start outside, we went in, they took out the other team, they hit a bomb outside the area, goal.
Nos tocó arrancar afuera, entramos, sacan al otro equipo, pegan un bombazo afuera del área, gol.
我们连球都没碰着，只好又出去了。
We didn't even touch the ball, we had to go out again.
No llevamos ni a tocar la pelota, tuvimos que salir de nuevo.
当我们出去时，他说好，现在我们要赢了，在我们必须进去的那一刻，我们不再出去了。
and when we went outside he said well now we are going to win and at that moment when we have to go in we don't go out anymore.
y cuando salimos fuera dijo bueno ahora vamos a ganar y en ese momento que nos toca entrar no salimos más
他抢球得分，抢球得分，抢球得分。
He grabbed the ball and scored, grabbed the ball and scored, grabbed the ball and scored.
agarraba la pelota y gol, agarraba la pelota y gol, agarraba la pelota y gol.
我们是观众，他把球传给了莫埃尔，他进球了。
We were spectators, he gave it to Moel and he scored the goal.
Nosotros éramos espectadores, se la daba a Moel y él hacía el gol.
那一刻我说，妈的。
And at that moment I said, shit.
Y en ese momento dije, mierda.
何等的决心。
What determination.
Qué determinación.
他做他想做的事，当他想做的时候，如果他想做的话，再见，一切都结束了。
He does what he wants, when he wants and if he wants, bye, it's over.
Hace lo que quiere, cuando quiere y si él quiere, chau, se acabó.
我的意思是，他有点不喜欢他们对阵他的进球，他说，就是这样，现在我们要赢了。
I mean, he didn't like the goal they scored against him one bit and he said, that's it, now we're going to win.
O sea, no le gustó ni un poco el gol que le hicieron y dijo, listo, ahora vamos a ganar.
下午就这样过去了。
And the afternoon was over.
Y se terminó la tarde.
就是这样。
And that's it.
Y ya está.
其他人也在旁边看着，纷纷议论，那我们现在怎么办？
And the others also watching and saying, now what do we do?
Y los otros también viendo y diciendo, ¿y ahora qué hacemos?
听我说，兄弟，建筑师。
Listen to me, brother, architect.
Escuchame, hermano, arquitecto.
即将收到。
is about to be received.
está a punto de recibirse.
你呢？
And you?
¿Y vos?
¿你的财产？
¿Your property?
¿Vos bien?
很好，谢谢。
Fine, thanks.
Bien, gracias.
因为我不知道。
Because I don't know.
Porque no sé.
我哥哥要...建造我的房子。
My brother about to... Make my house.
Mi hermano a punto de... Haceme la casa.
你稍微利用一下你的兄弟...我们会充分利用他。
You use your brother a little... We're going to get the most out of him.
Lo usas a tu hermano un poco de... Le vamos a sacar el jugo.
当然。
Of course.
Claro.
我哥哥明年即将以建筑师的身份毕业。
My brother is about to graduate as an architect next year.
Mi hermano está a punto de recibirse de arquitecto el año que viene.
我的会计师姐姐几年前也收到了。
My accountant sister also received a couple of years ago.
Mi hermana contadora también recibí hace un par de años.
她比我小。
She's smaller than me.
Es más chica que yo.
它组合得很好。
It is very well put together.
Está muy bien armado.
我们有房地产和良好的账户。
We have real estate and good accounts.
Tenemos real estate y bien las cuentas.
我们大家必须共同努力。
We all have to work together.
Tenemos que currar todos juntos.
我是唯一一个去了另一家分店的人。
I was the only one who went for another branch.
Yo fui el único que fue por otra rama.
但是，是的，事实是我有两个兄弟......
But yes, the truth is that I have two brothers who...
Pero sí, la verdad que tengo dos hermanos que...
他们非常有能力，并且就是这样开始他们的生活的。
They are very capable and have started their lives that way.
Son muy capaces y han iniciado su vida de esa manera.
很好，但是你想学习类似的东西还是成为一名教练？
Good, but do you want to study something similar or be a coach?
Bien, pero tenés ganas de estudiar algo parecido o con ser por ahí un coach?
我来自莫弗梅，也许我没有参加过很多远程课程。
I am from Moverme, perhaps I have not taken many distance courses.
Soy de Moverme, quizás no he hecho muchos cursos a distancia.
同样是房地产业务、会计。
same real estate business, accounting.
mismo de negocios inmobiliarios, de contabilidad.
金融活动，很多事情......
of financial activity, of a lot of things that...
de actividad financiera, de un montón de cosas que...
我参加了短距离课程，以保持自己的运动能力，而最终，其中一个让你
I have taken small distance courses to keep myself moving more than anything and in the end the one of that makes you
he hecho cursos chicos a distancia para mantenerme más que nada en el movimiento y al final la uno de eso le hace
对未来可能发生的事情敞开心扉。
open your mind to what may arise in the future.
abrir la cabeza con lo que puede llegar a surgir en un futuro.
踢球的时候也能看到明天。
and it also helps to see tomorrow when playing football.
y también ayuda a ver el día de mañana cuando juega el fútbol.
你想继续从事哪个分支，无论是与足球相关还是与其他方面相关。
What branch do you want to continue in, whether linked to football or also from another side.
en qué rama uno quiere seguir, ya sea ligado al fútbol y también desde otro lado.
听我说，如果我错了请纠正我，阿古斯蒂娜已经结婚了，对吗？
Listen to me, correct me if I'm wrong, Agustina already married, correct?
Escúchame, corregime si me equivoco, ¿Agustina ya casados, correcto?
你们在一起多久了？
How long have you been together?
¿Cuánto tiempo llevan juntos?
快13年了。
Almost 13 years.
Casi 13 años.
13岁，完美。
13 years old, perfect.
13 años, perfecto.
我想穿红头发的人会穿在你身上的衣服。
I want to wear things that maybe a redhead would wear on you.
Quiero usar cosas que quizás te ponga un colorado.
佩塞拉是一个浪漫主义者，他是一个陈腐的浪漫主义者。
Pescella is a romantic, he is a trite romantic.
Pescella es un romántico, es un romántico trillado.
有鲜花，就有惊喜。
There are flowers, there are surprises.
Hay flores, hay sorpresas.
我不会向自己扔花，因为后来你看到...
I'm not going to throw flowers at myself because later, you saw...
No voy a tirarme flores a mí mismo porque después, viste...
他们会反驳一切，但事实是我不太浪漫。
They will refute everything, but the truth is that I am not very romantic.
Van a refutar todo, pero la verdad es que no soy muy romántico.
我不是很浪漫。
I'm not very romantic.
No soy muy romántico.
拉菲科说他比卡罗更浪漫。
Lafico said he was more romantic than Caro.
Lafico dijo que él era más romántico que Caro.
但对此撒谎。
But lie about it.
Pero míntelo.
他很可爱。
He is very sweet.
Él es muy dulce de leche.
啊，这是牛奶汁。
Ah, it's dulce de leche.
Ah, es dulce de leche.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
我当时...
I at the time...
Yo en la época...
当我年轻的时候，也许我更喜欢这种类型的事情，现在他们会责备我一点。
When I was younger, maybe I was much more of that type of thing and now they reproach me a little bit.
más chico quizás era mucho más de ese tipo de cosas y ahora un poquito me lo recriminan.
我尽我所能。
I do what I can.
Hago lo que puedo.
听着，好吧，不是那样。
Listen, well, not that.
Escucha, y bien, eso no.
但你细心吗？
But are you attentive?
Pero, ¿sos atento?
是的，我喜欢它。
Yes I like it.
Sí, me gusta.
是的，有时候我有点。
Yes, sometimes I am a little.
Sí, a veces soy un poco.
沉重，用一种好的方式来说，试图...
heavy, to put it in a good way, trying to...
pesado, por decirlo en el buen sentido, de intentar que...
最后，由于从一侧到另一侧发生了如此多的变化，我们尽力确保她一切都好。
In the end, with so much change, so much change from one side to the other, we try to make sure she is well.
al final nosotros con tanto cambio, tanto cambio de un lado a otro, intentar de que ella esté bien
我可以很舒服，我们去的地方......它很重。
that I can be comfortable, that the places we go... It weighed well.
de que pueda estar cómoda, de que los lugares donde vayamos... Ha pesado bien.
是的，为了你的幸福，而你像阿戈尔迪一样，缺乏这种帮助。
Yes, for your well-being, which you lack, like Agordi, in helping you.
Sí, para su bienestar, que te falta, como es Agordi, en que te ayuda.
试图担心她是否会没事，除了跟着我之外……
of trying to worry a lot that she might be okay, that in addition to following me...
de intentar preocuparme mucho de que ella pueda estar bien, de que además de seguirme...
对我来说，因为我的职业生涯，她可以拥有一个经常搬家的女孩，她有她的动力，她可以
to me because of my career she can have a girl who moves a lot who has her motivations and who can
a mí por mi carrera ella pueda tenerse una chica que se mueve mucho que tiene sus motivaciones y que pueda
继续她的项目，她可以赋予它价值，因为最终它们是日复一日激励她的东西。
continue with her projects, that she can give value to that because in the end they are the ones that motivate her day by day.
seguir con sus proyectos, que pueda darle valor a eso porque al final son los que la motivan día a día.
听我说，运动员都是有条理的吗？
Listen to me, are all athletes methodical?
Escúchame, ¿todos los deportistas son metódicos?
培训、日程安排、罚款。
training, the schedule, the fine.
entrenamiento, el horario, la multa.
有些是，有些则较少。
Some yes, others less.
Algunos sí, otros menos.
食物。
The food.
La comida.
有些是，有些则较少。
Some yes, others less.
Algunos sí, otros menos.
罚款也是有原因的，因为有些人做得不太好。
The fines are there for a reason too, because there are some who are not so good.
Por algo están las multas también, porque hay algunos que no son tan buenos.
从1到10，你还好吗？
From 1 to 10, how are you?
Del 1 al 10, ¿cómo estás vos?
我认为我们的分数是 9.75。
And I think we are at 9.75.
Y yo creo que estamos en un 9,75.
啊，这么多。
Ah, that's a lot.
Ah, eso es un montón.
但因为我很普通，所以从这个意义上说我也有点紧张。
But because I am average, I am also a little intense in that sense.
Pero porque soy medio también en ese sentido soy un poco intenso.
痴迷。
Obsessive.
Obsesivo.
我还没有达到痴迷的地步，我不知道，但差不多了。
I don't get to the obsessive point, I don't know, but almost.
No llego, no sé si al punto obsesivo, pero casi.
我喜欢早到。
I like to arrive early.
Que me gusta llegar temprano.
你用什么打败自己，用什么惩罚自己而失败？
What do you beat yourself up with, what do you punish yourself with and fail?
¿Con qué te latigas, con qué te castigás y fallás?
嗯，这是我长期以来一直在做的事情，接受错误。
Well, that's something I worked on a lot over time, accepting being wrong.
Bueno, eso es algo que trabajé mucho con el tiempo, aceptarme el equivocarte.
但无论是在练习中，无论是在比赛中，还是在接受和规范中，都会犯错误。
but make mistakes whether in a practice, whether in a game, in accepting and normalizing.
pero equivocarte ya sea en una práctica, ya sea en un partido, en aceptar y normalizar.
高水平运动中发生的某些类型的事情。
certain types of things that happen in high performance sports.
cierto tipo de cosas que en el deporte de alto rendimiento suceden.
但我这个时候起床很有条理，我必须到达那里......
but then I'm very methodical about getting up at this time, I have to get there...
pero después soy mucho metódico de levantarme a esta hora, yo tengo que llegar...
训练前两个小时，按照自己的节奏做所有事情。
Two hours before training, do everything at my own pace.
dos horas antes de entrenamiento, hacer cada cosa a mi ritmo.
突然，交通堵塞了，我没有提前两个小时到达，而是提前了一个半小时到达。
One moment suddenly there is traffic and instead of arriving two hours early I arrive an hour and a half.
que un momento de repente hay tráfico y en vez de llegar dos horas antes llego una hora y media.
我已经感觉到有什么东西……有什么东西在我内心移动，你看。
And I already feel that something... something is moving inside me, you see.
Y ya me siento que algo... algo se me mueve, viste, adentro.
我对此有点沉重，我有自己的饮食习惯和诸如此类的事情。
I'm a bit heavy on that, I have my routines with eating and all that kind of stuff.
soy un poco pesado en eso, tengo mis rutinas con la alimentación y todo ese tipo de cosas.
但他们不会给你压力。
But they don't put pressure on you.
Pero no te la hacen la presión.
我走了两步，一个汉堡。
And I got two steps, a hamburger.
Y me clavé dos pisas, un hambúrguer.
不，你必须知道什么时候......作弊日可以，但不是每天。
No, you have to know when... Cheat day is fine, but not every day.
No, uno tiene que saber cuándo... El cheat day está bien, pero no todos los días.
你必须知道什么时候可以这样做，随着时间的推移，你会知道什么时候该做，什么时候不该做。
You have to know when you can do that and over time you learn when it is time and when it is not.
Uno tiene que saber cuándo puede hacer eso y con el tiempo vas aprendiendo cuál es el momento y cuándo no.
说真的，它很快。
Seriously, it's fast.
De verdad, es rápido.
它能为您做什么？
And what can it do for you?
¿Y qué te puede?
你在阿佩拉做什么？
What do you do in apera?
¿Con qué te la das en apera?
杜尔塞？
¿Dulce?
那？
That?
¿Qué?
冷冻？
Frozen?
¿Helado?
¿Po' choclo？
¿Po' choclo?
托尔塔。
Torta.
是的，蛋糕、冰淇淋，任何含有糖果的东西都是我必须远离的弱点。
Yes, cake, ice cream, anything that has sweets included is a weakness that I have to keep away from it.
Sí, torta, helado, todo lo que tenga dulce incluido es una debilidad que tengo que tenerlo ahí lejos.
每周一次，就这样，一点类似的事情。
once a week, like that, a little something like that.
una vez por semana, así, una cosita tipo.
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
一般来说...
Generally...
Generalmente...
除了与营养师一起研究之外，他们还告诉你，在比赛当天、比赛结束后......
In addition to working on it with nutritionists, they tell you, on the day of the game, after the game it is...
Además de trabajarlo con los nutricionistas, te dicen, el día del partido, después del partido es...
你允许的。
your allowed.
tu permitido.
如果你想吃披萨，那就吃披萨吧。
If you want to eat a pizza, eat a pizza.
Si querés comerte una pizza, comete una pizza.
比赛当天。
The day of the match.
El día del partido.
比赛当天或比赛结束后。
On the day of the game or after the game.
El día del partido o post partido.
这是你的许可。
It is your permission.
Es tu permitido.
第二天你必须恢复，所以你必须开始吃得好。
The next day you have to recover, so you have to start eating well.
Al día siguiente ya tenés que recuperar, así que tenés que empezar a comer bien.
但这就是他们允许你让你的头脑也看到松散的地方。
but that is where they have allowed you to let one in your head also see looseness.
pero ahí es donde te han permitido para que uno en su cabeza también viste afloje.
听我说，我带着半苦涩的心情结束了，因为这个想法是……
Listen to me, I close with a half bitter because the idea was...
Escúchame, cierro con una medio amarga porque la idea era...
自从他回到河床、解放者队、加拉多以来，一切都已经过去了一段时间了，已经一个月了。
that he returned to River, the Libertadores, Gallardo, everything has already passed for a little while, already a month.
que volvió a River, la Libertadores, Gallardo, todo ya pasó un tiempito, ya un mes.
但在河球场上你会看到博塔弗戈的冠军。
But on the River court you see Botafogo champion.
pero encima en cancha de River ves campeón a Botafogo.
你说……很痛，很痛。
You say that... It hurts, it hurts.
Decís que... Duele, duele.
多么痛苦啊，因为那是……并不是我为River武装起来，而是……
What a pain, because it was... It's not that I was armed for River, but it was...
Que dolor, porque era... No es que estaba armada para River, pero era...
是的，很痛，很痛，因为最后出现了一个巨大的幻象。
Yes, it hurts, it hurts, because in the end there was a huge illusion.
Sí, duele, duele, porque al final había una ilusión enorme.
我不会对你撒谎，我们都抱有很大的希望。
And I'm not going to lie to you, we all had that great hope.
Y no te voy a mentir, todos teníamos esa ilusión muy grande.
他甚至不想看比赛。
He didn't even want to see the game.
El partido no lo quería ni ver.
因为这是看台，这是我们的场地，我们本来可以在那里。
because it is the stands, it is our field and we could have been there.
porque es las tribunas, es nuestra cancha y podríamos haber estado ahí.
最后一切的发生都是有原因的。
In the end everything happened for a reason.
Al final todo pasó por algo.
我们无法实现它。
We couldn't achieve it.
No pudimos lograrlo.
但我认为一些事情正在开始，一些对未来非常有用的事情正在开始。
But I think that something is starting, something is starting that will be very useful for the future.
Pero yo creo que se inicia algo, se inicia algo que nos va a servir mucho para el futuro.
我的生活中有成千上万个坚持的例子，我们正在谈论坚持得最多的一个……
I have had thousands of examples of insisting in my life and we were talking about the one who insisted the most...
He tenido en mi vida miles de ejemplos de insistir y estuvimos hablando del que más ha insistido en...
我不知道在足球史上是否如此，但他坚持了很多，才在国家队取得了成就。
I don't know if in the history of football, but he has insisted a lot to achieve an achievement with the national team.
no sé si en la historia del fútbol, pero que mucho ha insistido para conseguir un logro con la selección.
最终的情况是依靠这一点，依靠这一点，然后......
And in the end the situation is to lean on that, lean on that and...
Y al final la situación es apoyarse en eso, apoyarse en eso y...
并努力尝试，显然希望很大，我们没有实现它，但是......
and to try and well, obviously the hope was great, we didn't achieve it, but...
y a intentarlo y bueno, obviamente que la ilusión era mucha, no la conseguimos, pero...
但是，嘿，我们肯定会报仇的。
But hey, we're going to have revenge for sure.
Pero bueno, vamos a tener revancha seguro.
今年你回归参加河床解放者队了吗？
Did you return for River's Libertadores this specific year?
¿Vos volviste por la Libertadores de River este año puntual?
不，我是从河回来的。
No, I came back through River.
No, volví por River.
当我在第一场比赛中回来时，他们问我
When I came back during one of the first games they asked me
Cuando volví justo en uno de los primeros partidos me preguntaron
在胡安·科帕的第一场比赛中，他们也问了我同样的问题。
for Juan Copa's first game and they asked me the same thing.
por el primer partido de Juan Copa y me preguntaron lo mismo.
我告诉他最后你会回来找River，River是……
And I told him in the end you come back for River and River is...
Y yo le dije al final uno vuelve por River y River es...
在杯赛中，在锦标赛中，无论什么，穿上顶级球衣就已经承担了很大的责任。
in cups, in tournaments, whatever, putting on the top shirt already has a very big responsibility.
en copas, en torneos, lo que sea, ya ponerte la camiseta de arriba ya tiene una responsabilidad muy grande.
对于解放者来说，这显然是终极梦想。
which obviously for Libertadores is the ultimate dream.
que obviamente para Libertadores es el sueño máximo.
明年还有世俱杯。
Next year there is the Club World Cup.
El año que viene está el Mundial de Clubes.
还有这个博卡，这个河床，这个国米，迈阿密……还有很多重要的比赛，但是……
And this Boca, and this River, and this Inter, Miami... There are many important competitions, but...
Y esta Boca, y esta River, y este Inter, Miami... Hay muchas competencias importantes, pero...
我又回来为河床效力了。
I came back to play for River again.
Yo volví por volver a jugar en River.
希望在...
Hopefully in the...
Ojalá en la...
我们正在命名的最佳技能，我希望它们附有一个头衔，这就是我们的愿望和渴望。
best skills that we are naming and I hope they come accompanied by a title and that is what we wish and long for.
mejores competencias que estamos nombrando y ojalá vengan acompañados de título y es lo que deseamos y anhelamos.
一个返回河流。
one returns for River.
uno vuelve por River.
好吧，听着，再次谢谢你，我还不能胜任。
Well, listen, thank you once again, I'm not up to it.
Bueno, escuchá, una vez más gracias, no estoy en condiciones.
是的，我可以邀请你打一场篮球。
Yes, I can invite you to play a little basketball.
Sí, te puedo invitar a jugar un picadito de básquet.
我们可以打篮球，毫无疑问，我们可以一起投篮。
We can play basketball, without a doubt, we can shoot hoops together.
Podemos jugar el básquet, sin duda, podemos tirar al aro juntos.
我们可以测量。
we can measure.
podemos medir.
让潘帕官方成为我们的总赞助商，并与您的朋友一起获得许可。
Keep Pampa Official as our gross sponsor who has a license with your friends.
Mantén Pampa Oficial es nuestro sponsor grosso que tiene licencia con tus amigos.
还有你和 River 的俱乐部，但我想向你展示这份伟大的礼物，毫无疑问是市场上最好的伴侣，看起来多么可爱。
and your club with River, but I want to show you this great gift, the best mate on the market without a doubt, look how cute.
y tu club con River, pero te quiero mostrar este regalazo, mejor mate del mercado sin dudas, mira que lindo.
给你拿去。
For you to take it.
Para que te lo lleves.
壮观。
Spectacular.
Espectacular.
萨卡洛
Sácalo
Sácalo.
触摸它，看着它，品味它。
Touch it, look at it and savor it.
Tocalo, miralo y saborealo.
一切，苦的，甜的，热的，没有真菌，壮观。
Everything, bitter, sweet, thermal without fungus, spectacular.
Todo, amargo, dulce, térmico sin hongo, espectacular.
巨大的。
Tremendous.
Tremendo.
我们将使用它。
We are going to use it.
Lo vamos a usar.
每个人都喜欢它。
Everyone liked it.
A todos les ha gustado.
那个已经有了，我不想给你压力，恩佐和庞蒂斯都有了。
That one already has it, I don't want to put pressure on you, Enzo and Pontius have it.
Ese ya lo tiene, no te quiero meter presión, lo tiene Enzo y Poncio.
布埃诺。
Bueno.
好吧。
Alright.
Está bien.
使用它
use it
Usalo.
我希望事情能保持这种状态，继续沿着这条路走下去。
I hope things stay that way then, that they continue down that path.
Espero que siga así la cosa entonces, que siga por ese camino.
如果您在 Instagram 上寻找他，请与专业粉丝交配。
mate professional fan if you look for him on Instagram.
mate fan profesional si lo buscan en Instagram.
德国人，再次感谢你，疯子，很高兴见到你，我祝贺你......
Germán, thank you again, crazy, it was a great pleasure to meet you, I congratulate you on...
Germán, nuevamente gracias loco, un placer enorme conocerte, te felicito por...
为了你的事业，一切。
for your career, everything.
por tu carrera, todo.
再次感谢 Mati 和 Rivers de Prensa 的所有人。
Once again, thanks to Mati and all the people at Rivers de Prensa.
Una vez más, gracias a Mati y a toda la gente de Rivers de Prensa.
谢谢你，达里奥，谢谢你的经理，我非常高兴。
Thank you, Dario, to your manager and a huge pleasure.
Gracias, Dario, a tu manager y un placer enorme.
太感谢了。
Thank you so much.
Muchas gracias.
再见。
See you soon.
Nos vemos pronto.
随机 Infobae 与 Germán Becerra。
Random Infobae with Germán Becerra.
Random Infobae con Germán Becerra.